[

    { 
        "question": "Whose death sparked World War I?",
        "choice1": "Kaiser Wilhelm",
        "choice2": "Archbishop Ussher",
        "choice3": "Queen Victoria",
        "choice4": "Archduke Franz Ferdinand",
        "answer": 4
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "The Best club in the History of Football?",
        "choice1": "Real Madrid",
        "choice2": "Bayern Munich",
        "choice3": "Barcelone",
        "choice4": "Ac Milan",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these nations was neutral in World War I?",
        "choice1": "Germany",
        "choice2":  "Norway",
        "choice3": "Italy",
        "choice4": "England",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question":  "Which weapon was first used at the Battle of the Somme in World War I?'",
        "choice1":" Submarine",
        "choice2":" Tank",
        "choice3": "Jet fighter",
        "choice4":" Chariot",
        "answer":  2
    },
    {
        "question": "The GOAT of Football",
        "choice1": "Messi",
        "choice2": "Pele",
        "choice3": "Maradona",
        "choice4": "Cristaino Ronaldo",
        "answer":  4
    },
    {
        "question": "World War I ended in:",
        "choice1": "1925",
        "choice2": "1918",
        "choice3": "1920",
        "choice4": "1915",
        "answer":  2
    },
    {
        "question":"Which of these battles did not involve Roman soldiers?",
        "choice1": "Arretium",
        "choice2": "Chalons",
        "choice3": "Cannae",
        "choice4": "Thermopylae" ,
        "answer":  4
    },
    {
        "question":"Where were the Aegean Bronze Age civilizations located?'",
        "choice1": "Algeria",
        "choice2": "India",
        "choice3": "Greece",
        "choice4": "Somalia",
        "answer":  3
    },
    {
        "question":"Who was the first U.S. president to appear on television?",
        "choice1": "Richard Nixon",
        "choice2": "Ronald Reagan",
        "choice3": "Abraham Lincoln",
        "choice4": "Franklin Delano Roosevelt",
        "answer":  4
    },
    {
        "question":"In which city would you find the Statue of Liberty?",
        "choice1": "San Francisco",
        "choice2": "New York City",
        "choice3": "Deyniile",
        "choice4": "Philadelphia",
        "answer":  2
    }
]